{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What was the most memorable moment we shared together?",
      "options": [
        "Our first date",
        "The time we traveled together",
        "When you surprised me on my birthday",
        "Every moment with you is special"
      ],
      "correctAns": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What's my full name including my nickname?",
      "options": [
        "Jerome R. Bulosan -agul",
        "Jerome R. Bulosan -agulit",
        "Jerom R. Bulan -agul",
        "Jerome Bulosan -agul"
      ],
      "correctAns": 0,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "What's my favorite food?",
      "options": ["Adobo", "Sinigang", "Caldereta", "Sinaing na Isda"],
      "correctAns": 1,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "What's my favorite anime?",
      "options": ["Jujutsu Kaisen", "One Piece", "Vinland Saga", "Overflow"],
      "correctAns": 3,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "What's my favorite color?",
      "options": ["Red", "Blue", "Green", "Black"],
      "correctAns": 3,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "Where did we first meet?",
      "options": ["Park", "School", "Cafe", "Mall"],
      "correctAns": 2,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "What's my favorite movie?",
      "options": ["Vivamax", "Harry Potter", "Alien", "Titanic"],
      "correctAns": 0,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "What's my dream job?",
      "options": [
        "Software Engineer",
        "Front-End Developer",
        "Police",
        "Quality Assurance"
      ],
      "correctAns": 1,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "Why i fall inlove with you",
      "options": ["Appearance", "Attitude", "Personality", "All of the Above"],
      "correctAns": 3,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "What's my favorite sport?",
      "options": ["Basketball", "Soccer", "Tennis", "Swimming"],
      "correctAns": 0,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "What's my favorite music genre?",
      "options": ["Pop", "Rock", "Jazz", "Classical", "All of the above"],
      "correctAns": 3,
      "points": 5
    }
  ]
}
